// creating an array and passing the number, questions, options, and answers
let questions = [
    {
    numb: 1,
    question: "Who developed Python Programming Language?",
    answer: "Guido van Rossum",
    options: [
      "Wick van Rossum",
      "Rasmus Lerdorf",
      "Guido van Rossum",
      "Niene Stom"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 2,
    question:"Which type of Programming does Python support?",
    answer: "all of the mentioned",
    options: [
        "object-oriented programming",
        "structured programming",
        "functional programming",
        "all of the mentioned"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 3,
    question: " Is Python case sensitive when dealing with identifiers?",
    answer: "yes",
    options: [
      "No",
      "yes",
      "machine dependent",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 4,
    question: "Is Python code compiled or interpreted?",
    answer: "Python code is both compiled and interpreted",
    options: [
      "Python code is both compiled and interpreted",
      "Python code is neither compiled nor interpreted",
      "Python code is only compiled",
      "Python code is only interpreted"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 5,
    question: "All keywords in Python are in _________?",
    answer: "None of the Above",
    options: [
      "Capitalized",
      "lower case",
      "UPPER CASE",
      "None of the Above"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 6,
    question: "What will be the value of the following Python expression=> 4 + 3 % 5?",
    answer: "7",
    options: [
      "7",
      "2",
      "4",
      "1"
    ]
  },
    {
    numb: 7,
    question: "Which keyword is used for function in Python language?",
    answer: "def",
    options: [
      "Function",
      "def",
      "Fun",
      "define"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 8,
    question: "Which of the following functions can help us to find the version of python that we are currently working on?",
    answer: "sys.version",
    options: [
      "sys.version(1)",
      "sys.version(0)",
      "sys.version()",
      "sys.version"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 9,
    question: "Python supports the creation of anonymous functions at runtime, using a construct called __________?",
    answer: "lambda",
    options: [
      "pi",
      "anonymous",
      "lambda",
      "None Of the Above"
    ]
  },

  {
    numb: 10,
    question: "What does pip stand for python?",
    answer: " Preferred Installer Program",
    options: [
      "Pip Installs Python",
      "Pip Installs Packages",
      " Preferred Installer Program",
      "All of the Above"
    ]
  },
  // you can uncomment the below codes and make duplicate as more as you want to add question
  // but remember you need to give the numb value serialize like 1,2,3,5,6,7,8,9.....

  //   {
  //   numb: 6,
  //   question: "Your Question is Here",
  //   answer: "Correct answer of the question is here",
  //   options: [
  //     "Option 1",
  //     "option 2",
  //     "option 3",
  //     "option 4"
  //   ]
  // },
];